

Profile



Romina Ghaderi



rominaa.ghaderi94@gmail. com



+46700182173



Brunskogsbacken 70 12371 FARSTA



portfolio-romigh94.vercel.app



linkedin.com/in/rominaghaderi-8b6074232



github.com/romigh94

Key skills

HTML/CSS/Sass	••••
Bootstrap	••••
Git/Github	••••
Javascript	••••
Vue.js	••••
React.js	••••
Node.js	••••
MongoDB	••••

Romina Ghaderi

About me

I am a 28-year-old girl with great ambitions and a deep passion for creating and developing creative solutions. I can understand and adapt to new technology, which makes me a fast learner. Others have described me as a person with a great commitment to my work.

Education

Frontend development

aug 2021 - jun 2023

Jensen yrkeshögskola, Kista

During this education I've learned to work with: HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Javascript, React.js, Vue.js, Next.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Git, UX/UI design, Figma and CI/CD pipelines.

Programming 1 (Java)

feb 2021 - feb 2021

Jensen komvux, Stockholm

High school degree

jan 2017 - dec 2017

Södertörns folkhögskola, Solna

Assistant nurse

2015 - 2016

Omsorgslyftets utbildningar, Älvsjö

Work experience

Frontend developer

apr 2023 - jun 2023

Les creatives, Stockholm

- Worked with: HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Figma, Javascript, Node.js, Vue.js. MongoDB, Vitepress and API development.
- Project examples: QR code generator, Documentation app, Video & Image compression, Diff/match/patch, Color picker and Favicon uploader

Frontend developer

nov 2022 - feb 2023

Webbfabriken, Stockholm

- Worked with: HTML, CSS, Sass, Boostrap, Javascript, Next.js, Node.js, MongoDB and API development.
- Project examples: I designed and developed 3 different websites.

Assistant nurse

2020 - 2021

Vardaga, Fisksätra

Assistant nurse Attendo, Solna 2018 - 2020

D - (- ... - . - .

References

References will be provided after request